quizzyn.com 2015-10-30

# Privacy Policy | QuizZyn.com

## QUIZZYN’S PRIVACY POLICY

Quizzyn is committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an online privacy policy that guides how we collect, store, and use information collected about you online.

### WHAT INFORMATION DOES QUIZZYN.COM COLLECT?

Quizzyn may request and/or collect non-private information from you when you use Quizzyn.com and/or register. For the protection of your privacy, we ask that you avoid sending us any and all personally identifiable information.

### COOKIES

Quizzyn may use cookies to improve the use of our websites. A "cookie" is a small file that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. We do not use cookies to store personally identifiable information. Additionally, Quizzyn may use cookies and third party vendors to deliver ads related to Quizzyn to you while you are surfing other websites. If you would like to opt-out of such ads, you may visit https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ to opt-out of such use of cookies.

### IP ADDRESSES

Quizzyn may collect your IP address for safety and security purposes.

### LOG FILES

Other non-personal information collected by Quizzyn is in the form of logs - files that record website activity, including how many "hits" a particular web page is getting (a.k.a., "click-through data"). For example, log file entries are generated every time a visitor clicks the "Home" icon on our site. These entries enable Quizzyn to assess overall site activity, and improve the general user experience. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain information about your system such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer) and the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS).

### LINKING TO THIRD PARTY SITES

Quizzyn may provide links from our Web sites to third party Web sites and we encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information to them. Quizzyn assumes no responsibility for the content found on third party websites linked from Quizzyn.com. Quizzyn hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site.

### ADVERTISEMENTS ON QUIZZYN

Quizzyn permits the use of advertising on Quizzyn.com by third party advertisers. Some advertising partners may use cookies or similar technologies to better measure campaign effectiveness, target future campaigns and deliver a more targeted experience to users. Advertisers must comply with personal data guidelines, including the Data Protection Act 1998, to ensure our users’ personal data is protected. Additionally, all advertisers are instructed by Quizzyn not to display ads with sexual, violent or drug & alcohol related themes. Should you find an inappropriate or offensive advertisement on Quizzyn, please notify us by emailing [support@quizzyn.com](mailto:support@quizzyn.com). Additionally, third parties may collect certain types of information about your visits to Quizzyn, including interaction with content on Quizzyn.

### GENERAL

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Quizzyn.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance. We hope you have a great experience on Quizzyn. Feel free to approach us on [support@quizzyn.com](mailto:support@quizzyn.com).
